{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567621526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567621526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567631438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567631438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567633522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567633522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567635604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567635604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567638717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567638717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567640925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567640925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567643122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567643122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567645903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567645903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567648059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567648059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567650367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567650367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567653548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567653548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567655601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567655601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567657672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567657671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567660633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567660633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567662824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567662824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567665012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567665012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567668022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567668022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567670332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567670331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567672644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567672644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567675621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567675621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567677725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567677725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567679811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567679811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567682875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567682874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567685037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567685037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567687213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567687213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567691602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567691602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567694011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567694011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567696423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567696423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567699655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567699655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567701891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567701891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567704108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567704108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567707042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567707041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567709223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567709223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567711414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567711414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567714321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567714320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567716648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567716648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567719007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567719006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567722103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567722101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567724464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567724464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567726831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567726831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567729810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567729810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567732105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567732104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567734375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567734375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567737674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567737674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567739964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567739962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567742253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567742253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567745649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567745649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567748104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567748104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567750523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567750523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567753331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567753330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567755469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567755469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567757626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567757626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567761024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567761024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567763355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567763355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567765656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567765656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567768900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567768898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567771159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567771159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567773420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567773419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567776456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567776456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567778655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567778655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567780800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567780799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567783988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567783988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567786250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567786250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567788512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567788511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567791742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567791741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567793983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567793983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567796196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567796196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567799470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567799470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567801816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567801816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567804152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567804152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567807261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567807261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567809623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567809623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567811959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567811959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567815358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567815357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567815476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567815475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567839842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567839842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2e63cd49-8a9e-4cee-819e-4cc64b3ff776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567850990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567850988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" DAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567853644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567853644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" DAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567855358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567855358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dereva"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567861767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567861767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dereva"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567863446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567863446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567867255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567867255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567868831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567868830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567872000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567871999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567873622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567873622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" debe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567876760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567876760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" debe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567878325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567878325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dobi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" DOBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567881197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567881197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dobi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567882754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567882754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567886300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567886299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567887855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567887855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567891283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567891282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567893300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567893300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567893581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567893581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b93e0ad2-488a-4d8a-a701-03157e36f5a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567906268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567906267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567907271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567907271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567907466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567907466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567908118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567908118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567908693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567908693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567909182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567909181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567909618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567909618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567910069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567910069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567910275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567910272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567910867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567910866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567911362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567911360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567914042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567914041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567914652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567914652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567915187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567915186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567915418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567915417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567915813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567915813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567916595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567916595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567918814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567918814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567919265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567919265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567919469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567919469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567920215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567920215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567921069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567921068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567921556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567921555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567921731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567921730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567922359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567922358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" SAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567922474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567922474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567923017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567923016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567924392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567924390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567927564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567927563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567928457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567928457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567928704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567928704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567929196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567929196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567929360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567929360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567929912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567929911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567930670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567930670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" MITATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567932075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567932075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567932579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567932579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567933598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567933596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567934213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567934212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" UWEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567934402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567934401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567935055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567935055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567937616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567937616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567938222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567938222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567939023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567939023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567939668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567939668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567940140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567940139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567941058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567941058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TALANTA"," userResponse":" TALANTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567944260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567944259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567945107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567945105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENDA"," userResponse":" ALITENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567945584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567945583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567946523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567946522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567947348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567947348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567948114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567948113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567948667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567948667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567948905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567948904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567949286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567949286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567949892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567949891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567951095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567951095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567951787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567951787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567953673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567953673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567954447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567954447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567955402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567955402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567956025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567956025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKETI"," userResponse":" KUKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567956214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567956214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567956595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567956595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567957230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567957230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567957736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567957736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567958565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567958565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJADILI"," userResponse":" KUJADILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567959008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567959008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567959632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567959631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHIMU"," userResponse":" MUHIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567962510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567962510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567962711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567962711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567963305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567963305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567964153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567964153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567964768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567964768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567965508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567965508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567965901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567965900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567966084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567966084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567966477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567966477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567967248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567967248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567970093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567970092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" WALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567970966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567970965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567971690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567971690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567971935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567971935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567972620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567972620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567973089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567973089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567973724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567973724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567974408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567974408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567976993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567976993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567977766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567977766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567977973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567977973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567978358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567978357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567978788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567978788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567979277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567979277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567982549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567982549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567983476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567983476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567984240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567984240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567985067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567985067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567985712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567985711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567988051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567988051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567988655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567988655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567989605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567989604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567990660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567990660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567991833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567991832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567993155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567993155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" UNAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567993510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567993510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567994046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567994046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567994560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567994560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567995465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567995465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567998540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567998540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567999802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567999802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568000606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568000606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUJA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568000888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568000888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568001662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568001662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568004470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568004470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZISIKIA"," userResponse":" NAZISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568005153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568005153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568005787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568005787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568006421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568006421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568007445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568007445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZIIMBA"," userResponse":" NAZIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568010687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568010687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568013565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568013565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568014468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568014468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568015007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568015007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568015751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568015751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568016683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568016683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568017584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568017584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOHISI"," userResponse":" ALIPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568018123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568018123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568020673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568020673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568021976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568021975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568022943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568022943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568023908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568023908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568025181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568025180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568025901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568025901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568028368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568028368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568029213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568029213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568032815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568032815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUATIA"," userResponse":" KUFUATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568035475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568035475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568036029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568036029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568036500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568036500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568037432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568037432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568040740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568040740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568041290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568041289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568041759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568041759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568041931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568041931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568042707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568042707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568043671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568043671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568044426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568044426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568045031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568045031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568045855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568045855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ANGEMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568048369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568048368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568049491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568049490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUBALI"," userResponse":" ANGEKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568050060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568050060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568050764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568050764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568051268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568051268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568054323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568054322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568060143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568060143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568060904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568060904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568061650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568061649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568062014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568062014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568062809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568062809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" WALIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568063631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568063630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568064787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568064787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568065588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568065588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568066132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568066132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568068790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568068790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568069489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568069489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568070108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568070107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568070890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568070890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568071575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568071575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568071761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568071761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568072202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568072202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568072712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568072712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568075496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568075495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568075877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568075877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568076698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568076697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568077518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568077517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568078288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568078288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568080867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568080866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568081673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568081673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568084230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568084229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568085097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568085097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568085734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568085734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568086418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568086417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568086583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568086583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568086931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568086931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568087754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568087754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568088572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568088572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568089434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568089434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" AMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568091894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568091894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568092549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568092549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568093073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568093073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568094472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568094472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568095036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568095036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568095650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568095650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568096030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568096029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568096894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568096894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPWEKE"," userResponse":" UPWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568097729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568097729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568100886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568100886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568102059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568102059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568104522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568104520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568105494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568105493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ATAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568106121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568106121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568107010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568107010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568107846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568107846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568108375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568108375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568108856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568108856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568111614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568111613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568112138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568112138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568112669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568112669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568113813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568113813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIDHARAU"," userResponse":" WALIDHARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568114356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568114356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568114810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568114810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568117240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568117240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568117453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568117453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568118637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568118636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568120933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568120933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568121116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568121116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568121831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568121830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568122904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568122904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568125722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568125722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNADHANI"," userResponse":" UNADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568126126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568126126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568126461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568126461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568127474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568127474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" UTAMSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568130493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568130493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568131119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568131119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568131835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568131835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568132655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568132655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUKATA"," userResponse":" HAKUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568133213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568133213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568135335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568135335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568135727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568135727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568136155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568136155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568136693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568136693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568137091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568137090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568137587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568137586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568138581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568138581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568139193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568139190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYO"," userResponse":" MOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568141733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568141733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568142726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568142726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568142889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568142889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568143709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568143708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568145584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568145584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNITULIZA"," userResponse":" HUNITULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568146033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568146033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568146564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568146564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568146774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568146774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568147312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568147310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568150132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568150132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ZITAMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568151100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568151099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568151332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568151332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568151581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568151580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568154977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568154977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568156041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568156041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568156966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568156965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568157947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568157947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568158358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568158357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568158951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568158951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568160424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568160423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMWELEKEZE"," userResponse":" AMWELEKEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568161106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568161106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568161510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568161510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568161910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568161910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568162111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568162110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568162508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568162507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568163234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568163234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568166541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568166541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568167124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568167124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568167218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568167218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568167811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568167810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568168354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568168354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568168861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568168861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568169500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568169500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568170109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568170109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568170569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568170569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568171163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568171163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568172222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568172222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568174493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568174492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568175158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568175157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568176035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568176035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568176315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568176315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568176803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568176803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568177657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568177656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568178602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568178602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIANZA"," userResponse":" KILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568179634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568179633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568180328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568180328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568180983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568180983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568184080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568184079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFANYI"," userResponse":" WAFANYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568184621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568184620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568185352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568185352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568186364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568186363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568186906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568186906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568187520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568187520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568188466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568188466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIZOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568189287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568189287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568192736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568192736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" WALISIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568193347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568193347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568194380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568194380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTAMU"," userResponse":" MTAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568194533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568194533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568195234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568195234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568197611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568197611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568198298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568198298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568199158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568199157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568199769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568199769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568200538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568200538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568201836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568201836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568202866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568202865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFAULU"," userResponse":" ALIYEFAULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568203642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568203642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568204122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568204122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568206684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568206684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568207351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568207351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568207868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568207868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568208734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568208733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568209610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568209610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAWEZA"," userResponse":" ATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568210754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568210754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568213942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568213942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568214992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568214992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKAMILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKAMILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568215535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568215534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568215877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568215876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568216431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568216431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568217524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568217524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568218306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568218306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568227317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568227317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568227581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568227581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568228235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568228235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568228850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568228849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKA"," userResponse":" ALITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568229219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568229218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568229690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568229690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568230324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568230324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568230483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568230483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568231088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568231088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568232707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568232707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568233521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568233521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568234207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568234207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568242316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568242316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568242551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568242551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568242943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568242935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568244096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568244095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568244619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568244619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568245353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568245353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUJA"," userResponse":" WALIKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568245908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568245908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568246743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568246742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEMBEBA"," userResponse":" WAMEMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568247207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568247207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568247952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568247952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568248597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568248597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHELA"," userResponse":" MACHELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568252310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568252310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" WALIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568252795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568252795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568252969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568252969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568253674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568253674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568254289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568254289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568255725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568255725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHAPWA"," userResponse":" AMECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568256170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568256170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568256795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568256794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUACHWA"," userResponse":" KUACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568257249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568257249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568257454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568257454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568258028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568258028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568261175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568261175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568261875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568261874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568263208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568263208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568263978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568263978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568265353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568265353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568265734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568265734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568266173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568266173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568266793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568266793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568269836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568269835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMZAWADI"," userResponse":" ALIMZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568270789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568270789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568271212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568271212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568272194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568272194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLIWAZA"," userResponse":" KUMLIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568275367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568275367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568276363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568276363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568276608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568276608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568277230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568277230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568278239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568278239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568278957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568278956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568279556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568279556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568280266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568280265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568281328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568281326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIWA"," userResponse":" KUSAIDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568282184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568282182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568282709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568282709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568285288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568285288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568285379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568285379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" b87563af-d810-4802-91c5-e3c99ce87f06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568294502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568294502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_h-z-d"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568297467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568297467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-h-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568301985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568301985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_s-f-d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568305784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568305784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-g-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568310130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568310130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_y-t-d"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568313852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568313851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-u-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568318312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568318312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-o-t"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568321760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568321760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_z-d-a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568325156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568325156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_v-d-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568328818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568328818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_o-d-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568334606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568334599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_d_o-d-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568342841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568342839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" e88306b5-398a-499b-94b0-950c44636b1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_d_o-d-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568353908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568353908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_f-w-d"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568381579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568381579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_t-d-w"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568385179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568385178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_h-s-d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568394117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568394117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-t-s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568414318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568414318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_h-d-j"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568417640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568417640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-n-k"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568450378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568450378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_g-d-n"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568454032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568454032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_s-j-d"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568477459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568477458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_a-d-p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568481148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568481147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_r-d-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568486911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568486911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 9b3bf289-84bd-4dc5-a07c-b757d291fbc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_d_r-d-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568498362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568498362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568499246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568499246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568499890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568499889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568500103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568500103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568500786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568500786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568501119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568501119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568501620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568501620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568504680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568504680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568505004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568505004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568505617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568505617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568506810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568506810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAPENDANA"," userResponse":" TUNAPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568507583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568507583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568510411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568510410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITUMWA"," userResponse":" TUKITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568511375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568511374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568512157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568512157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568515069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568515069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568515513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568515512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568516355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568516355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITUMWA"," userResponse":" NILITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568516968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568516968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568517121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568517121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568517595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568517595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568517990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568517990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568519624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568519624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKANUNUE"," userResponse":" NIKANUNUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568520415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568520415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568520951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568520951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568521676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568521676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568524496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568524495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIENDA"," userResponse":" NILIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568524765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568524765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568525317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568525317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568528466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568528466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568529408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568529408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568530541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568530540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIWAONA"," userResponse":" TULIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568531137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568531137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568532002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568532002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568533261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568533260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568533792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568533792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568533965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568533965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568534485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568534485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568537887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568537887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568539260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568539260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITAMANI"," userResponse":" NILITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568539900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568539900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568540531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568540531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568541131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568541131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568541304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568541304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568544307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568544306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISEMA"," userResponse":" NILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568545103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568545103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568548507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568548507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568552047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568552047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568552592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568552592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568553846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568553846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568554606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568554606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUWAOMBE"," userResponse":" TUWAOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568555244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568555244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568555658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568555658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568556613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568556613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568558975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568558974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568559634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568559634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568560259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568560259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568560482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568560482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568561180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568561179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568564223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568564222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568565264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568565264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALINIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568566387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568566386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568566880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568566879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568567747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568567747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568568510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568568509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568569019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568569018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TURUDI"," userResponse":" TURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568569657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568569657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568572777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568572776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568573646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568573646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568574137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568574137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568575275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568575275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568575878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568575878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568576383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568576383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568579029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568579028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIENDA"," userResponse":" TUKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568579834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568579834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568580567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568580566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568581896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568581896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATATURUHUSU"," userResponse":" HATATURUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568585681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568585679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUBALIWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUBALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568585892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568585892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568586759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568586759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568587964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568587964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUKACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568588528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568588527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568597050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568597049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568601435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568601434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLIKIPA"," userResponse":" GOLIKIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568610635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568610635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJITAHIDI"," userResponse":" NILIJITAHIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568611420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568611420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDAKA"," userResponse":" KUDAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568612034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568612034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568614764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568614764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZANGU"," userResponse":" WENZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568615728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568615727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568616322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568616322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUNGA"," userResponse":" KUFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568616801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568616801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568617508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568617508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568617980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568617980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568620978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568620978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568622332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568622332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TULIOCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568623525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568623525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568623749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568623748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568624574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568624574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" MCHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568625719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568625719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGI"," userResponse":" MWINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568628406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568628406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGOLI"," userResponse":" MAGOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568629171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568629171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568629776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568629776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568630359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568630359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568631213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568631213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568634041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568634041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568634256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568634256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568635109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568635109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568636155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568636155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568636949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568636949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568637735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568637735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568638433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568638432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUWA"," userResponse":" HATUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568638640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568638640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568639196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568639196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568642046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568642045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568643023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568643023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568645842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568645842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568647128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568647128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKEMEA"," userResponse":" ALINIKEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568648128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568648128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ACHA"," userResponse":" ACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568648625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568648625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568650663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568650663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568651124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568651122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568659028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568659028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITAKA"," userResponse":" ULITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568659115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568659114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568659220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568659220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 2c97d951-1703-48bb-bb70-7a85149d2482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITAKA"," userResponse":" ULITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568674672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568674672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568678308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568678308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568681587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568681587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568684708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568684707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568689013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568689013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568692014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568692014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568695329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568695329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568698743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568698743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568701643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568701643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568705019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568705019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568708145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568708145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568711307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568711307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568714112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568714112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568717363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568717363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568724436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568724436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568727748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568727748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568730930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568730930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568734331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568734331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568737659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568737659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568740669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568740669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568743666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568743665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568747192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568747192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568750915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568750914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568754236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568754236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568759718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568759718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568765481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568765481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568771385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568771384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568789710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568789709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c05fbd2a-d352-461a-b374-766e25cc924a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568821387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568821387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568821917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568821917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568825074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568825074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568826172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568826171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIBEBA"," userResponse":" ALINIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568826748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568826748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568827219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568827219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568827904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568827904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LETU"," userResponse":" LETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568828420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568828420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568828935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568828935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568829051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568829051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568830006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568830006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBULUU"," userResponse":" KIBULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568830628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568830628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568831436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568831435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja babangu alinibeba katika gari letu la rangi ya kibuluu kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568834155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568834155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TULISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568834807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568834807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568835781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568835781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZUNGUKO"," userResponse":" MZUNGUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568836817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568836817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568837402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568837402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568838566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568838566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIGEUKE"," userResponse":" ZIGEUKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568839280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568839280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisimama kwenye mzunguko tukisubiri taa zigeuke kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568855923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568855923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWONA"," userResponse":" NILIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568858476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568858475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568859555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568859555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEVAA"," userResponse":" ALIYEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568860032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568860031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568860927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568860926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568861520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568861520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568862036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568862036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568862150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568862150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568862974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568862974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568864591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568864590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568865367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568865367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBENI"," userResponse":" PEMBENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568865580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568865580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568866465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568866465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilimwona mwanamke aliyevaa nguo nzuri ya rangi ya machungwa akitembea pembeni mwa bararabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARARABARA"," userResponse":" BARARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568871045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568871045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amefunga kiunoni mshipi mkubwa mwekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568871990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568871989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amefunga kiunoni mshipi mkubwa mwekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFUNGA"," userResponse":" AMEFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568873182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568873182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amefunga kiunoni mshipi mkubwa mwekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIUNONI"," userResponse":" KIUNONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568873976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568873976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amefunga kiunoni mshipi mkubwa mwekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHIPI"," userResponse":" MSHIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568874650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568874650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amefunga kiunoni mshipi mkubwa mwekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568875414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568875414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amefunga kiunoni mshipi mkubwa mwekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MWEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568878867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568878867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONONI"," userResponse":" MKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568879679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568879679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHIKA"," userResponse":" ALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568880363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568880363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKOBA"," userResponse":" MKOBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568880509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568880509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568881114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568881114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568881219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568881219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568882074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568882074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkononi alishika mkoba wa rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568885607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568885607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUUNI"," userResponse":" MIGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568886552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568886552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAA"," userResponse":" ALIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568887507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568887507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568887817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568887817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568888393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568888392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568888537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568888537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568889395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568889395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568889682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568889682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568890718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568890718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISIGINO"," userResponse":" VISIGINO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568891446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568891446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIREFU"," userResponse":" VIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568894738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568894738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568895325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568895325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568896441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568896441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568896715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568896714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568897414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568897414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUSA"," userResponse":" KUGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568897849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568897849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568898483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568898483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568899026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568899026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu alisimama na kugusa nywele zake refu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568901845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568901844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKIWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568903090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568903090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" ZIMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568904093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568904093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568904361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568904360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568905194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568905194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568905900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568905900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBANO"," userResponse":" KIBANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568906132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568906132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568906739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568906739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568906834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568906834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568907692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568907692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zilikiwa zimeshikiwa katikati kwa kutumia kibano cha rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568911331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568911329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568912708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568912708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" AKIREKEBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568913374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568913373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBANO"," userResponse":" KIBANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568913996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568913994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568932163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568932163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568932223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568932222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568932398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568932398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" bd10d655-3841-44d4-a3f6-dd4c3928c82a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akirekebisha kibano chake cha nywele mkoba wake ulianguka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568953729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568953728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568957150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568957150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568960431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568960431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568963664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568963664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568972162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568972162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568975425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568975425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568978667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568978667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568982018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568982018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568985374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568985374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568993641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568993641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548568996999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548568996998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569000311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569000311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569003365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569003365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569006168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569006168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569009000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569009000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569012331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569012331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569015524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569015524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569020005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569020004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569023307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569023307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569030305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569030305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569033681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569033681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569038472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569038472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569041544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569041544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569044952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569044952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569049149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569049148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569052399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569052398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569058199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569058199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569070035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569070035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 3f580366-8e2f-446b-ac98-b99066410671"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569081099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569081099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569093411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569093411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569095023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569095023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569098970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569098970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569100551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569100551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569104560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569104560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569106572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569106571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569106923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569106923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 824530d9-7385-42c4-a4fb-3e778c37e3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569118205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569118205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569119012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569119012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569119225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569119225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569119883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569119883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569120841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569120841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569121609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569121609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569122461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569122461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569122724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569122724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569123418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569123418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569124124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569124124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569126434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569126433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569126982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569126982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569128234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569128233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" ALIPOZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569128988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569128988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569129678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569129677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569130736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569130736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFARIKI"," userResponse":" ALIFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569134000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569134000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569134135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569134134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569135089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569135089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFILIWA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569135283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569135283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569135918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569135918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569136444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569136444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569137841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569137840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIMFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569138526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569138526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569139301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569139301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569140414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569140414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569140633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569140633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569141208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569141208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569143660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569143660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569144256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569144256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569145162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569145162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569146226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569146226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AKIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569146794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569146794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569147534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569147534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569148434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569148434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569149000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569149000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569150007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569150007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569151363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569151363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569152372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569152372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569159401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569159401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569167350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569167350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569168254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569168253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569168588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569168588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569169299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569169298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569170233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569170233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569171178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569171177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569173734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569173733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569174301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569174300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569175736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569175735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569176596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569176595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASWA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569178093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569178092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569179238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569179238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINA"," userResponse":" AKINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569179794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569179794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569180460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569180459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569181078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569181078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569181296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569181295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569181880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569181880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569182379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569182379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569185598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569185598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569186106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569186106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569186882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569186881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569188568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569188567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569189223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569189223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569189437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569189437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569189652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569189652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569193705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569193704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569194184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569194183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569194789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569194789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569195499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569195497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569195777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569195777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569196304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569196303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569199023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569199022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569200490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569200490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569200855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569200855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569201632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569201632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569202478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569202478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569203323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569203323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569204121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569204120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569207368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569207368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569208832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569208832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" ALIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569209398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569209398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569212353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569212352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569213329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569213329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569213954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569213954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569214432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569214432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569215329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569215329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569216217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569216217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569216833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569216833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" WAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569217302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569217302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569218413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569218412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" WAMWONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569218854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569218854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569219863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569219863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569220461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569220461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569223727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569223727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569224624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569224624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569224880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569224880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569225739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569225739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569226377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569226376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTOWE"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569227327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569227327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569229970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569229970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569230518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569230517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569231734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569231734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569232630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569232630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569233698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569233698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" AKIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569234573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569234573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569237558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569237558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569238233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569238233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569238426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569238426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569239273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569239273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569240100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569240100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALA"," userResponse":" AKILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569240658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569240658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569240844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569240843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569241361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569241361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569244758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569244758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569246055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569246055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569246991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569246991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569247757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569247756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569248375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569248375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569248974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569248974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569249531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569249531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569252368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569252367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569253468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569253468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569254545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569254544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569254981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569254980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569255633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569255633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569256995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569256995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569257863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569257862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569258400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569258400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569259147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569259147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569265431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569265431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569265884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569265884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569267029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569267029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569268114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569268114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569269072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569269071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569271584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569271584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569272754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569272754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569275273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569275273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569276005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569276005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569278808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569278807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569279866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569279865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569282202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569282202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569283198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569283197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569284423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569284423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIRUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569285697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569285697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569286093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569286093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569286955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569286954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569287571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569287570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569288382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569288382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569291675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569291675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569292259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569292258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569293766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569293766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569294525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569294525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569294761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569294760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569295209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569295208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569296122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569296122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569297312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569297312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569298453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569298452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569299190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569299190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569299407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569299407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569300414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569300414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569303312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569303312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569303870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569303870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569304649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569304649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569305226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569305226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569306396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569306395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569307366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569307366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569307871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569307871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569308700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569308700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569311672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569311672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569312307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569312307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569312533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569312533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569313573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569313573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569314595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569314595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569315403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569315403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569316585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569316585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569316911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569316911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569317921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569317921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569318582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569318582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569321615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569321614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569322905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569322905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569323969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569323968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" WAANGALIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569326367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569326367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569326881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569326881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLETE"," userResponse":" MLETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569327456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569327456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569331152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569331152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569331577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569331577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569332261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569332261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569333076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569333076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MIKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569333680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569333680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569334236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569334236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569335442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569335441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" KUMBARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569339126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569339126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569339591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569339590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569340297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569340297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569341023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569341023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569342058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569342058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569343094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569343094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569343432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569343432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569344217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569344217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569347172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569347172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569348028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569348028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569349216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569349216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" KIFUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569349431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569349431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569350197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569350197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569351073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569351073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569353808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569353807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569354016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569354016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ca5733a2-e3f3-4a31-88da-081bc97c6c38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569369007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569369007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_b-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569372196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569372196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-e-n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569375321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569375321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-e-k"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569378765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569378765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-m-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569382784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569382784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_d-o-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569385918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569385917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_g-e-z"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569389073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569389073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_e-t-m"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569405054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569405054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_i-e-t"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569412079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569412079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_l-e-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569416124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569416124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_f-h-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569421918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569421918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_f-h-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569431886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569431885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 88e2ba69-138a-41bf-829d-e21d265f6324"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_f-h-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.87","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569464684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569464684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ad364e97-ebd5-4ca5-99f4-bcaa45f267e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.87"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_n-e-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.87","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569468294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569468289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ad364e97-ebd5-4ca5-99f4-bcaa45f267e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.87"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_n-e-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569561141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569561141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" ad364e97-ebd5-4ca5-99f4-bcaa45f267e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.87"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_n-e-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569561249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569561249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" 0a1aed3c-2ed2-4aa9-8927-55a265ab4a7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569571972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569571972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569574952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569574952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569576509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569576509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569579816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569579815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569581416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569581416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569584471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569584471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569586055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569586055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569589120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569589120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569590693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569590693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569593807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569593807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569595370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569595370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569602349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569602349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569603958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569603958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569606255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569606254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569607997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569607997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569610185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569610185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569611769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569611769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569614125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569614125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569615702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569615702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569618129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569618128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548569619534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548569619533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_084012"," gameId":" c0ff9a5f-1ec8-4366-ad91-07cff7cac9c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}